{
	"title": "Numbers",
	"total": 3,
	"courses": [
		{
			"id": 1,
			"title": "0-1-2-3",
			"quizzes": [
				{
					"id": "0",
					"explanation": "This is number \"0\"",
					"question": "What number is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
						"correct": "0"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "1",
					"explanation": "This is number \"1\"",
					"question": "What number is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
						"correct": "1"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "2",
					"explanation": "This is number \"2\"",
					"question": "What number is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
						"correct": "2"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "3",
					"explanation": "This is number \"3\"",
					"question": "What number is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
						"correct": "3"
					}
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"id": 2,
			"title": "4-5-6",
			"quizzes": [
				{
					"id": "4",
					"explanation": "This is number \"4\"",
					"question": "What number is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["4", "5", "6"],
						"correct": "4"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "5",
					"explanation": "This is number \"5\"",
					"question": "What number is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["4", "5", "6"],
						"correct": "5"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "6",
					"explanation": "This is number \"6\"",
					"question": "What number is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["4", "5", "6"],
						"correct": "6"
					}
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"id": 3,
			"title": "7-8-9",
			"quizzes": [
				{
					"id": "7",
					"explanation": "This is number \"7\"",
					"question": "What number is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["7", "8", "9"],
						"correct": "7"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "8",
					"explanation": "This is number \"8\"",
					"question": "What number is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["7", "8", "9"],
						"correct": "8"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "9",
					"explanation": "This is number \"9\"",
					"question": "What number is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["7", "8", "9"],
						"correct": "9"
					}
				}
			]
		}
	]
}